<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!--   CMETS Profile Schema Version 1.0  -->

<METS_Profile xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS_Profile/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:mets="http://www.loc.gov/METS/"
xsi:schemaLocation="
      http://www.loc.gov/METS_Profile/
      http://www.loc.gov/standards/mets/profile_docs/mets.profile.v1-2.xsd
      http://www.loc.gov/METS/
      http://www.loc.gov/standards/mets/mets.xsd
    ">
    <URI LOCTYPE="URL">http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/mets/cmets</URI>
    <title>Canadiana.org Trustworthy Digital Repository METS Profile</title>
    <abstract>
        This profile documents the standard for supplying and encoding metadata within the Canadiana.org TDR.
    </abstract>
    <date>2017-04-19T12:00:00Z</date>
    <contact>
        <name>Julienne Pascoe</name>
        <institution>Canadiana.org</institution>
        <address>440 Laurier Ave. West, Suite 200, Ottawa ON K1R 7X6, Canada</address>
        <phone>613-235-2628</phone>
        <email>julienne.pascoe@canadiana.ca</email>
    </contact>
    <related_profile/>
    <extension_schema>
        <name>MARCXML MARC 21 Schema</name>
        <URI>http://www.loc.gov/MARC21/slim</URI>
        <context>Used for encoding descriptive metadata at the series or document level. Preferred for bibliographic material.</context>
    </extension_schema>
    <extension_schema>
        <name>Simple Dublin Core Container</name>
        <URI>http://dublincore.org/schemas/xmls/qdc/2008/02/11/simpledc.xsd</URI>
        <context>Alternate format for encoding descriptive metadata at the series or document level. Suitable for simple
            records, but see the description rules below for use guidelines.</context>
    </extension_schema>
    <extension_schema>
        <name>DCMI Metadata Terms</name>
        <URI>http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/</URI>
        <context>Dublin Core elements used within a Simple Dublin Core record.</context>
    </extension_schema>
    <extension_schema>
        <name>IssueInfo</name>
        <URI>http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/issueinfo</URI>
        <context>Used to encode issue metadata and linking information for issue records.
        </context>
    </extension_schema>
    <extension_schema>
        <name>ALTO</name>
        <URI>https://www.loc.gov/standards/alto/v3/alto.xsd</URI>
        <context>A standardized XML format used to store layout information and OCR for document pages. This format is preferred
            over the other accepted OCR format, txtmap.</context>
    </extension_schema>
    <extension_schema>
        <name>Txtmap</name>
        <URI>http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/txtmap</URI>
        <context>Used to encode OCR or other full text for document pages.</context>
    </extension_schema>
    <extension_schema>
        <name>JHOVE XML Handler Output Schema</name>
        <URI>http://hul.harvard.edu/ois/xml/xsd/jhove/jhove.xsd</URI>
        <context>JHoVE XML output may be included within the administrative techMD element. For details on JHOVE see http://hul.harvard.edu/jhove/.</context>
    </extension_schema>
    <description_rules>
        <p>
            MARC Records should follow standard cataloguing rules (i.e. AACR2 or RDA).
        </p>
        <p>
            Dublin Core records may use any of the standard DC elements. It is recommended to use the DC recommended guidelines
            best practices for usage. During the creation of internal data structures for access, these fields
            will be interpreted in specific ways:
        </p>
        <p>
            If there is one dc:date field, it will be treated as the date of publication. If there are two or more dc:date
            fields, the first two will be treated as the start and end of a publication date range. Additional
            dc:date fields are ignored. To guarantee the correct parsing of dates, they should be ISO 8601-compliant
            dates in one of the following formats: YYYY, YYYY-MM, YYYY-MM-DDTHH:MM:SS.sssZ.
        </p>
        <p>
            The dc:language field(s) will be used to determine the language(s) of the document. ISO 639-3 language codes should
            be used. Other formats might not be parsed correctly.
        </p>
    </description_rules>
    <controlled_vocabularies/>
    <structural_requirements>
        <metsHdr>
            <requirement>
                <p>The OBJID attribute must uniquely identify the object among all of the submitter's content. It
                    must be between 5 and 64 characters in length and consist only of ASCII alphanumeric characters
                    and the underscore (A-Za-z0-9_).
                </p>
            </requirement>
        </metsHdr>
        <dmdSec>
            <requirement>
                <p>There must be a &lt;dmdSec&gt; element for the main item (series, issue or monographic document).
                    If the item is a document (issue or monograph) it may also contain child &lt;dmdSec&gt; elements
                    for each page in the &lt;structMap&gt;.
                </p>
            </requirement>
            <requirement>
                <p>The content of each &lt;dmdSec&gt; element must be an inline record wrapped in an &lt;xmlData&gt;
                    element or an &lt;mdRef&gt; element. The record format depends on the type of object it references:</p>
                <p>For series and monographic documents, it must be a MARCXML record or a Simple Dublin Core record.</p>
                <p>For issues, it must be an IssueInfo record.</p>
                <p>For components, there are legacy METS records that have txtmap records stored as a dmdSec. As of
                    this version of our proile, all Txtmap data is optional and will be stored as files rather
                    than described as metadata. A Txtmap in a dmdSec or in a file element will be treated as equivalent.</p>
            </requirement>
        </dmdSec>
        <amdSec>
            <requirement>
                <p>Items with components and associated files (documents or issues) may contain an amdSec for the
                    main item with techMD sections for each component.</p>
            </requirement>
            <requirement>
                <p>Each amdSec contains at least one techMD element. Each techMD element contains technical metadata
                    that corresponds to a file in the files directory of the containing Bagit archive.
                </p>
            </requirement>
            <requirement>
                <p>Each techMD element is provided an ADMID. This version of the profile supports the techMD sub-element
                    and the technical metadata file: JHOVE.
                </p>
            </requirement>
            <requirement>
                <p>Each techMD element contains an mdRef element referencing the location of the XML file containing
                    the administrative metadata. The MDTYPE attribute is set to "OTHER" and the OTHERMDTYPE attribute
                    set to the metadata scheme of the file. Other optional attributes are MIMETYPE and LABEL.</p>
            </requirement>
            <requirement>
                <!-->Upgrade to latest METS v2 will include example attributes: EXAMPLES="ex01"-->
                <p>For JHOVE files the following attributes are required: MIMETYPE, LOCTYPE, MDTYPE, OTHERMDTYPE,
                    xlink:href. See Example 1.</p>
            </requirement>
        </amdSec>
        <fileSec>
            <requirement>
                <p>
                    Series records may have one &lt;fileGrp&gt; with USE="canonical" although the canonical use value is being deprecated. Document records may also have &lt;fileGrp&gt;
                    elements with USE="master" and, optionally, USE="distribution".
                </p>
                <p>
                    There are two ways of grouping files: by fileGrp use such as Master or Distribution or by their component representation
                    (for instance all files that refer to a page). The first option, by fileGrp use, is being deprecated.
                </p>
                <p>
                    If the files are grouped by use, the master images for each page in a document are placed in the master group and
                    the PDF of the document is placed in the distribution group.
                </p>
                <p>
                    If the files are grouped according to their referent, ie all manifestations of the component (eg a page of a volume
                    or issue) are grouped into the same fileGrp, the use of each file is indicated at the file
                    level.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Use is first determined at the file level. Each &lt;file&gt; element may have a USE attribute containing one of
                    the following values: "master" or "derivative". If a file element does not contain a USE attribute
                    then this information will be acquired from the parent fileGrp USE attribute.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Each file element must contain an FLocat element which specifies external location of the content file in its xlink:href
                    attribute.The FLocat element must contain an xlink:href attribute, as well as a LOCTYPE attribute
                    indicating the type of href being provided.
                </p>
                <p>
                    The file element must also contain the following attributes: an ID for identifying this element and a MIMETYPE
                    for the data file being referenced. Other optional attributes include: SIZE, CREATED, CHECKSUM,
                    CHECKSUMTYPE.
                </p>
                <p>
                    An ADMID attribute on each file attribute points to the technical metadata for that file held within the amdSec.
                </p>
                <p>
                	The attribute USE="canonical" is being deprecated, it was previously used to indicate the principal URI associated with the 
                	resource. This was created for use with the CMR profile, which has now been deprecated.
                </p>
            </requirement>
        </fileSec>
        <structMap>
            <requirement>
                <p>
                    There must be a single &lt;structMap&gt; element with attribute TYPE="physical".
                </p>
                <p>
                    The root &lt;div&gt; element must have the attribute TYPE="document" for monographic documents, TYPE="series" for
                    a series metadata submission and TYPE="issue" for a document that is part of a series. Series
                    have no further &lt;div&gt; elements and must not have any &lt;fptr&gt; elements, as they are
                    metadata-only submissions. Documents and issues must have one &lt;div&gt; element for each
                    page they contain, appearing in sequential order. A document should include a &lt;fptr&gt;
                    to a distributable PDF version of the document as a whole, if one exists.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Each part of a document must be represented by a &lt;div&gt; with the attribute TYPE="page". If there is a master
                    image file for that page then it must contain a &lt;fptr&gt; which references the master image
                    file for that page. Note that a page in this context might not correspond to one physical page
                    of the original book (e.g. if the book was digitized with two facing pages for each image,
                    or if a large fold-out is split into multiple images). In some cases, such as with born-digital
                    content, there will not be a master image for each page, but one file for the entire object.
                    A &lt;fptr&gt; referencing the image file for each page is not required in these instances.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Each &lt;div&gt; element must contain a LABEL attribute to describe the item. For a series or monographic document,
                    it should be the common title of the item. For an issue, it should be the issue title without
                    the common series title (e.g., "vol. 5, issue 1 : January 1895"). For a page, it should be
                    the page number, sequence, or similar description (e.g. "p. 9" or "Front Cover").
                </p>
                <p>
                    Each &lt;div&gt; element must include a DMDID attribute which references the ID attribute of the corresponding
                    &lt;dmdSec&gt; element.
                </p>
            </requirement>
        </structMap>
        <structLink>
            <requirement>
                <p>
                    The mdRef and FLocat elements use the xlink:href attribute to point to external resources. For these elements the
                    attribute LOCTYPE can be set to "URI" or "URL". If set to URL, the path is relative to the
                    METS file, and includes the directory and corresponding name of the file as it appears in the
                    directory. If set to URI, and the element is FLocat, the files are located in the files directory.
                    If the element is mdRef then the files are located in the metadata directory.
                </p>
            </requirement>
        </structLink>
    </structural_requirements>
    <technical_requirements>
        <content_files>
            <requirement>
                <p>
                    Master images must be encoded as TIFF with GROUP 4 compression or uncompressed, JPEG or JPEG 2000.</p>
            </requirement>
            <requirement>
                <p>
                    Filenames may consist only of the following ASCII characters: A-Za-z0-9._ and -.
                </p>
                <p>
                    The stated MIME type for a given file indicates the type of file it is based on established file format standards.
                </p>
            </requirement>
        </content_files>
    </technical_requirements>
    <tool/>
    <!-->Example elements are included with the most recent version of METS v2
    <Example ID="ex01">
        <mets:amdSec>
            <mets:techMD ID="jhove.master.MississaugaTimes_2.1">
                <mets:mdRef LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="metadata/0001.jpg.jhove.xml" MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="jhove"
                />
            </mets:techMD>
        </mets:amdSec>
    </Example>
    -->
    <Appendix NUMBER="1">

        <?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
        <mets:mets xmlns:mets="http://www.loc.gov/METS/" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" OBJID="b2148559_001">
            <mets:dmdSec ID="dmd.b2148559_001">
                <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="issueinfo">
                    <mets:xmlData>
                        <issueinfo xmlns="http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/issueinfo">
                            <series>b2148559</series>
                            <title>Trade and Industrial Development Program quarterly activity report Asia and Pacific
                                = Programme d'expansion commerciale et industrielle rapport trimestriel des activités
                                Asie et Pacifique. --</title>
                            <sequence>1</sequence>
                            <language>fra</language>
                            <published>1987</published>
                            <pubstatement>[Ottawa] : Affaires extérieures Canada, 1987-1990</pubstatement>
                            <identifier>CA1 EA676 T712 EXF</identifier>
                            <note>Bilingual</note>
                            <note>b2148547</note>
                        </issueinfo>
                    </mets:xmlData>
                </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:dmdSec>
            <mets:dmdSec ID="dmd.b2148559_001.1">
                <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="txtmap">
                    <mets:xmlData>
                        <txtmap xmlns="http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/txtmap">
                            <page>
                                <t>CAI EA676 T712 EX F 1987dîw. 3rnal Affairs Affaires extérieures iada Canada STORAGE
                                    TRADE AND INDUSTRIAL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM PROGRAMME D’EXPANSION COMMERCIALE
                                    ET INDUSTRIELLE QUARTERLY ACTIVITY REPORT b RAPPORT TRIMESTRIEL DES ACTIVITÉS
                                    ^èCxfli ■c ASIA AND PACIFIC ASIE ET PACIFIQUE NON • CIRCULATING J CONSULTER
                                    SUR PLACE Dept, of External Affairs Mio. des Affaires extérieures J AN 14 1933
                                    RETURN Tû DEPARTMENTAL RETOURNER A LA LIBRARY BIBLIOTHEQUE OU MINISTERE APRIL
                                    - JUNE 1987 (1st QUARTER FY 1987-88) AVRIL - JUIN 1987 (1er TRIMESTRE, AF 1987-88)

                                </t>
                            </page>
                        </txtmap>
                    </mets:xmlData>
                </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:dmdSec>
            <mets:dmdSec ID="dmd.b2148559_001.2">
                <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="txtmap">
                    <mets:xmlData>
                        <txtmap xmlns="http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/txtmap">
                            <page>
                                <t/>
                            </page>
                        </txtmap>
                    </mets:xmlData>
                </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:dmdSec>
            <mets:dmdSec ID="dmd.b2148559_001.3">
                <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="txtmap">
                    <mets:xmlData>
                        <txtmap xmlns="http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/txtmap">
                            <page>
                                <t>14 Allalres extérieures Canada External Allairs Canada External Affairs Canada
                                    Affaires extérieures Canada Security /SfcurllJ Security /S4r urlli TO/1 GGB,
                                    RGB, ROB, LGB, UGH GGB, RGB, RGB, LGB, UGB UNCLASSIFIED Acceeelon/R4f4rwnce
                                    FROM/OF TO/1 UNCLASSIFIED Acctnl on/R6tSrenc e FROM/DE * IMT IHT Flle/Do»»ler
                                    File /Oo«« 1er REFERENCE • RÉFERENCE REFERENCE • RÉFÉRENCE SUBJECT SUJET QUARTERLY
                                    ACTIVITY REPORT 7 Grlohpr 19R7 SUBJECT SUJET RAPPORT TRIMESTRIEL SUR LES ACTIVITÉS
                                    7 octobre 1987 Number//Vvmrfro Numbtr/Num/is TPP-0438 TPP-0438 ENCLOSURES ENCLOSURES
                                    ANNEXES ANNEXES 1&gt;- H3 W - W ill DISTRIBUTION In the Department's continuing
                                    efforts to Improve the management of the Export and Investment Promotion Program,
                                    I am pleased to see that we are now able, In this Quarterly Trade Tracking
                                    Report, to display the progress being made by posts In the execution of the
                                    planned activities as outlined in the export and Investment promotion plans
                                    submitted by each post last fall. This review of progress will improve our
                                    ability to keep abreast of developments In your posts In a more disciplined
                                    fashion. This report will enable you and your officers to monitor the progress
                                    of program Implementation in your posts by comparing planned activities In
                                    priority sectors with quarterly activity highlights and results. It joins the
                                    Quarterly Results and Activity Report which has been, and will continue to
                                    be sent to you. On the whole I am pleased with the quality of the progress
                                    reports submitted by the posts. Sane missions have taken particular care to
                                    set out precise activity statements In their plans which have made their quarterly
                                    activity and results summaries In this report very effective program evaluation
                                    tools. I vculd hope that those posts who have not yet Indicated a carmencement
                                    of their planned activities will be more forthcoming in their next report.
                                    Our ability to continue to defend and build upon our current level of trade
                                    and Investment resources abroad will be Increasingly dependent upon the reliability
                                    of Information your posts provide to identify their activities, workload and
                                    results which the tracking system was designed In part to accomplish. 7, G.E.
                                    Shannon Deputy Minister International Trade DISTRIBUTION Je suis heureux de
                                    constater que, dans le cadre des efforts que le Ministère ne cesse de déployer
                                    pour améliorer la gestion du Programme de promotion des exportations et des
                                    investissements, ncus sarnies maintenant en mesure, dans le présent rapport
                                    trimestriel sur les activités et les résultats, d'indiquer les progrès accomplis
                                    par chacune des missions dans la réalisation des activités prévues dans les
                                    plans de promotion des exportations et des Investissements qu'elles ont présentés
                                    l'automne dernier. En raison de cet examen des progrès, nous serons mieux en
                                    mesure de nous tenir au courant, de façon plus disciplinée, des développements
                                    qui surviennent dans vos missions. Grâce au rapport, vos agents et vous pourrez
                                    comparer les activités prévues dans les secteurs prioritaires aux activités
                                    qui se sont déroulées et aux résultats qui ont-été obtenus au cours d'un trimestre
                                    et, par conséquent, surveiller les progrès réalisés en ce qui concerne la mise
                                    en oeuvre du programme dans vos missions. Ce rapport s'ajoute au Rapport trimestriel
                                    sur les activités et les résultats qui vous a été envoyé jusqu'ici et qui continuera
                                    de vois être transmis. Dans l'ensemble, je suis satisfait de la qualité des
                                    rapports d'étape qu'ont présentés les missions. Certaines missions ont pris
                                    bien soin d'établir des énoncés d'activités précis dans leurs plans, ce qui
                                    fait des résumés trimestriels sur les activités et les résultats que renferme
                                    le rapport susmentionné des eut Ils très efficaces d'évaluation du programme.
                                    J'ose espérer que les missions qui n'ont pas encore signalé avoir entrepris
                                    les activités qu'elles avaient prévues se montreront plus coimunlcatives dans
                                    leur prochain rapport. Notre aptitude 3 continuer de maintenir et d'accroître
                                    notre niveau actuel de ressources en matière de ccnmerce et d'Investissements
                                    â l'étranger reposera de plus en plus sur la qualité des renseignements que
                                    vos missions nous transmettent pour déterminer les activités, la charge de
                                    travail et les résultats pour lequel le système de suivi a, en partie, été
                                    mis sur pied. Le sous-mlnlstre du Commerce extérieur, 7G.E. Shannon

                                </t>
                            </page>
                        </txtmap>
                    </mets:xmlData>
                </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:dmdSec>
            <mets:dmdSec ID="dmd.b2148559_001.4">
                <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="txtmap">
                    <mets:xmlData>
                        <txtmap xmlns="http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/txtmap">
                            <page>
                                <t>AVIS IMPORTANT IMPORTANT Nous avons voulu donner à ce nouveau rapport une présentation
                                    qui soit aussi lisible que possible et rectifier quelques irrégularités et
                                    problèmes liés à 1'entrée des données et aux réponses présentées par les missions,
                                    ce qui a retardé la publication de la première édit ion. Vous remarquerez que
                                    dans les pages suivantes, nombre de sections devant contenir les données des
                                    missions ont été laissées en blanc. C'est parce que celles-ci n'ont pas fait
                                    rapport de leurs activités trimestrielles dans les secteurs qu'elles ont identifiés
                                    dans leur plan comme étant des secteurs prioritaires (voir page 30 du Guide
                                    et les instructions sur le formulaire 'Rapport des activités et des résultats'
                                    , sous la rubrique "Activités de promotion des exportations"). Autrement dit,
                                    le système est programmé uniquement pour comparer les activités et les résultats
                                    trimestriels avec les activités prioritaires énoncées dans le plan annuel de
                                    la mission. Un certain nombre de missions ont présenté des rapports d'activités
                                    trimestrielles pour des secteurs autres que ceux qui ont été identifiés dans
                                    leur plan annuel, de sorte qu'il devient impossible à leur Direction générale
                                    de surveiller les activités prioritaires planifiées pour la période. The first
                                    edition of this new report has been delayed by efforts to configure the report
                                    in as readable a format as possible and to deal with some anomalies and teething
                                    problems associated with mission responses and data entry. Readers will note
                                    that many of the sections for post inputs on the following pages are blank.
                                    This is a result of missions not providing quarterly activities on the sectors
                                    they identified in their plans as being their post priorities (see guide page
                                    30 ; see Tracking report form instructions under "Export Promotion Activities).
                                    Put another way, the system is programmed only to compare quarterly activities
                                    and results with priority activities outlined in the post annual Plan. A number
                                    ,of posts provided quarterly activities statements for sectors other than those
                                    they identified in their annual plan, thereby making it impossible for their
                                    bureaux to monitor their intended priority activities. For this first report
                                    only, the actual activities reported by posts who did not conform' to instructions
                                    have been included as section 2 as an indication that those posts in fact submitted
                                    quarterly activity reports. Future editions of this report will also include
                                    "Special Activities in Export and Investment Promotion Program" as submitted
                                    by posts in their quarterly tracking eports. As well future editions will be
                                    published within hirty days of the cut off date for the submission of quarterly
                                    reports by missions. L, Pour ce premier rapport seulement, nous avons présenté,
                                    dans la section 2, les activités réelles dont ont fait rapport les missions,
                                    contrairement aux instructions, afin d'indiquer qu'elles ont effectivement
                                    présenté des rapports d'activités trimestrielles. JJ La section "Activités
                                    spéciales dans le cadre du Programme de promotion des exportations et des investissements",
                                    telle que présentée par les missions dans leur Rapport des activités et des
                                    résultats, figurera dans les éditions ultérieures. En outre, celles-ci seront
                                    publiées dans les 30 jours qui suivent la date limite de présentation des rapports
                                    trimestriels par les missions. NOTICE

                                </t>
                            </page>
                        </txtmap>
                    </mets:xmlData>
                </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:dmdSec>
            <mets:dmdSec ID="dmd.b2148559_001.5">
                <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="txtmap">
                    <mets:xmlData>
                        <txtmap xmlns="http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/txtmap">
                            <page>
                                <t>ASIA &amp; PACIFIC ASIE ET PACIFIQUE Mission Page Bangkok 1 Canberra 6 Dhaka 8
                                    Hong Kong 13 Islamabad 17 Jakarta 21 Kuala Lumpur 26 Manila 34 Melbourne 38
                                    New Delhi 43 Osaka 48 Peking 52 Seoul 58 Shanghai 66 Singapore 70 Sydney 77
                                    Tokyo 83 Wellington 94 ■a

                                </t>
                            </page>
                        </txtmap>
                    </mets:xmlData>
                </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:dmdSec>
            <mets:dmdSec ID="dmd.b2148559_001.6">
                <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="txtmap">
                    <mets:xmlData>
                        <txtmap xmlns="http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/txtmap">
                            <page>
                                <t/>
                            </page>
                        </txtmap>
                    </mets:xmlData>
                </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:dmdSec>
            <mets:dmdSec ID="dmd.b2148559_001.7">
                <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="txtmap">
                    <mets:xmlData>
                        <txtmap xmlns="http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/txtmap">
                            <page>
                                <t>QUARTERLY PROGRESS REPORT OF EXPORT PROMOTION PROGRAM AT MISSIONS ABROAD FOR FISCAL
                                    YEAR 87 FORECAST OF KEY ACTIVITIES AND ANTICIPATED RESULTS STATED IN MISSION'S
                                    ANNUAL PLAN REPORT 4 87/09/25 POST :504-BANGK0K 005-C0MM. 1 &amp; INFORM. EQP.
                                    8&lt; SERV THAILAND ACTIVITIES PROPOSED IN POST PLAN: PLANNING: PAGE : ANTICIPATED
                                    RESULTS: ALL SUB-SECTORS POST FOLLOWING UP WITH VISITORS FROM TELECOMS SECTOR
                                    WHO VISITED EXPO'86 UNDER CIDA SPONSORSHIP. INTRODUCTION OF NEW CANADIAN FIRMS
                                    AND TECHNOLOGIES TO THAI MARKET. ONGOING FOLLOW-UP IN AREAS OF OPPORTUNITY
                                    AS IDENTIFIED IN 1986 CONSULTANT'S REPORT ON THAI TELECOMMUNICATIONS SECTOR.
                                    INTRODUCTION OF NEW CDN TECHNOLOGIES,PARTI­ CULARLY TO STATE RAILWAY,ELECTRICITY
                                    GENER­ ATING AUTHORITY,?, MINISTRIES. OFFICIALS OF COMMUNICATIONS AUTHORITY
                                    OF THAILAND TO ATTEND ITU CONFERENCE IN VANCOUVER, JULY 1988. TOUR OF CANADIAN
                                    TELECOM INDUSTRY TO FOLLOW. INTRODUCTION OF NEW CANADIAN FIRMS TO THAI MARKET.
                                    MONITOR PROGRESS OF 5TH AND 6TH PROJECTS OF TELEPHONE ORGANIZATION OF THAILAND.
                                    IDENTIFY OPPORTUNITIES ANS ASSESS LEVEL OF COMPETITION. COMPETITIVE BIDS SUBMITTED
                                    BY ESTABLISHED FIRMS. TRACKING: ACTIVITIES UNDERTAKEN IN QUARTER: QUARTERLY
                                    RESULTS REPORTED: QUARTER: 1 ARRANGE RECEPTION FOR VISIT OF SINCLAIR VOLK,
                                    MANAGER SPECTRUM MANAGEMENT, DOC OTTAWA. QUARTER 2 QUARTER 3 QUARTER: 4 i NINE
                                    ATTENDED EVENT. INTELLIGENCE OBTAINED LED TO LNS'S PARTICIPATION IN TENDER
                                    FOR FREQUENCY MONITORING VAN.

                                </t>
                            </page>
                        </txtmap>
                    </mets:xmlData>
                </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:dmdSec>
            <mets:dmdSec ID="dmd.b2148559_001.8">
                <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="txtmap">
                    <mets:xmlData>
                        <txtmap xmlns="http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/txtmap">
                            <page>
                                <t>REPORT 4 87/09/25 QUARTERLY PROGRESS REPORT OF EXPORT PROMOTION PROGRAM AT MISSIONS
                                    ABROAD FOR FISCAL YEAR 87 FORECAST OF KEY ACTIVITIES AND ANTICIPATED RESULTS
                                    STATED IN MISSION'S ANNUAL PLAN POST :504-BANGK0K PLANNING: 007-POWER &amp;
                                    ENERGY EQUIP. THAILAND PAGE ; 2 S&lt; SERV. ACTIVITIES PROPOSED IN POST PLAN:
                                    ANTICIPATED RESULTS: ALL SUB-SECTORS PREPARATION AND DISTRIBUTION OF A MARKET
                                    OPPORTUNITIES STUDY TO CANADIAN COMPANIES. TO INCREASE AWARENESS IN CDA OF
                                    THIS MARKET WHERE TWO CANADIAN COMPANIES HAVE ALREADY ENJOYED REMARKABLE SUCCESSES.
                                    ASSIST CANADIAN COMPANIES TO LOCATE RELIABLE LOCAL REPRESENTA­ TIVES AND TO
                                    GIVE RECOMMENDATIONS ON HOW TO PURSUE MAJOR PROJECTS INFORM CANADIAN COMPANIES
                                    OF OPPORTUNITIES WHICH WILL RESULT IN INCREASING MARKET SHARE. HAVE FREQUENT
                                    CONTACTS WITH EGAT FOR POTENTIAL THERMAL b HYDRO PROJECTS. INCREASE AWARENESS
                                    OF CANADA AS A POTENTIAL SOURCE OF SUPPLY AND SERVICES. FOLLOW UP FUTURE PROCUREMENT
                                    RE MAE MÜH UNIT 10 POWER BOILER. FURTHER SALES OF POWER BOILERS TO EGAT. TRACKING:
                                    ACTIVITIES UNDERTAKEN IN QUARTER: QUARTER: 1 INVITE TWO SENIOR EGAT OFFICIALS
                                    TO VISIT CANADA ON POWER TRANSMISSION AND DISTRIBUTION MISSION. QUARTER: 2
                                    QUARTER: 3 QUARTER: 4 QUARTERLY RESULTS REPORTED: TWO ASSISTANT GENERAL MANAGERS
                                    FROM EGAT VISITED CDA DURING 13-27 JUNE AND WERE IMPRESSED WITH CDN CAPABILITY
                                    IN POWER SECTOR.

                                </t>
                            </page>
                        </txtmap>
                    </mets:xmlData>
                </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:dmdSec>
            <mets:dmdSec ID="dmd.b2148559_001.9">
                <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="txtmap">
                    <mets:xmlData>
                        <txtmap xmlns="http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/txtmap">
                            <page>
                                <t>QUARTERLY PROGRESS REPORT OF EXPORT PROMOTION PROGRAM AT MISSIONS ABROAD FOR FISCAL
                                    YEAR 87 FORECAST OF KEY ACTIVITIES AND ANTICIPATED RESULTS STATED IN MISSION'S
                                    ANNUAL PLAN REPORT 4 87/09/25 POST :504-BANGK0K 3 008-TRANSPORT SYS, EQUIP,
                                    COMP, SERV. THAILAND ACTIVITIES PROPOSED IN POST PLAN. PLANNING: PAGE : ANTICIPATED
                                    RESULTS: ALL SUB-SECTORS I MASS RAPID TRANSIT:MINISTER OF INTERIOR HAS BEEN
                                    INVITED TO VISIT THE CANADIAN INSTALLATIONS, AT PRIVATE AND PUBLIC EXPENSE.
                                    THIS MINISTER WILL BE PIVOTAL DECISION MAKER ON WHO GETS CONTRACT AWARD. ANTICIPATED
                                    IN 1988. THE Cl DA FUNDED CONVERSION OF A PILOT SET OF ENGINES HAS YET TO BE
                                    TRANSFERRED FROM CANADA TO THAILAND. SUBSEQUENT SIX MONTHS OF TESTING COULD
                                    LEAD TO TECHNOLOGY AND EQUIPMENT PURCHASES. PREPARATION OF RECOMMENDED STRATEGIC
                                    PLAN TO MAXIMIZE CANADIAN OPPORTUNITY TO LAND MASS RAPID TRANSIT PROJECT. POSSIBILITY
                                    OF UP TO $1. 5 BILLION IN BUSINESS PROVISION OF QUALIFIED ENGINEERING PERSONNEL
                                    (CIDA FUNDED IF POS­ SIBLE) TO EXPRESS TRANSIT AUTHORITY TO BUILD-IN AS MUCH
                                    PRO-CANADIANISM AS POSSIBLE. COULD LEAD TO SPECIFICATIONS THAT FAVOUR CANADIAN
                                    SYSTEMS. PURSUE ALL OPPORTUNITIES TO PROMOTE SALE OF CANADIAN AIRCRAFT INCLUDING
                                    PARTS AND REPAIR SERVICES. SALES WORTH TOTAL OF *50 MILLION. ACTIVITIES UNDERTAKEN
                                    IN QUARTER: TRACKING: QUARTER: 1 PRESENTATION TO STATE RAILWAY OF THAILAND
                                    ON CDN CAPABILITIES. QUARTER 2 QUARTER: 3 QUARTER 4 QUARTERLY RESULTS REPORTED:
                                    SRT RECOMMENDED SOME LOCAL COMPANIES TO POST FOR POSSIBLE CDN REPRESENTATION.
                                    POST RECEIVED FROM SRT STANDARD SPECIFICATIONS FOR RAIL COACHES, LOCOMOTIVES,
                                    ETC.

                                </t>
                            </page>
                        </txtmap>
                    </mets:xmlData>
                </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:dmdSec>
            <mets:dmdSec ID="dmd.b2148559_001.10">
                <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="txtmap">
                    <mets:xmlData>
                        <txtmap xmlns="http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/txtmap">
                            <page>
                                <t>REPORT 4 87/09/25 QUARTERLY PROGRESS REPORT OF EXPORT PROMOTION PROGRAM AT MISSIONS
                                    ABROAD FOR FISCAL YEAR 87 FORECAST OF KEY ACTIVITIES AND ANTICIPATED RESULTS
                                    STATED IN MISSION'S ANNUAL PLAN POST :504-BANGK0K PLANNING: Oil-OIL PAGE :
                                    4 GAS EQUIPMENT, SERVICES THAILAND ACTIVITIES PROPOSED IN POST PLAN: ANTICIPATED
                                    RESULTS: ALL SUB-SECTORS îj PETRO CANADA INTL ASSISTANCE CORP. WORKING TO CONCLUDE
                                    TECHNICAL COOPERATION AGREEMENT WITH PETROLEUM AUTHORITY OF THAILAND, MORE
                                    ACTIVE INVOLVEMENT OF PCIAC ?&lt; CANADIAN SUPPLIERS IN THAI MARKET. PARTICIPATION
                                    BY AMBASSADOR IN ADVISORY BOARD TO PETROLEUM INSTITUTE OF THAILAND (PTIT).
                                    CLOSER TIES TO PTIT AS VEHICLE FOR INTRODU­ CING CANADIAN TECHNOLOGY. MEET
                                    WITH SENIOR OFFICIALS OF DOMESTIC AND FOREIGN OIL COMPANIES TO INTEREST THEM
                                    IN CANADIAN OIL AND GAS PRODUCTION &amp; PROCESSING EQUIPMENT AND CAPABILITY.
                                    INCREASE LEVEL OF VISITS OF THAI BUYERS TO CANADA, LEADING TO EVENTUAL INCREMENTAL
                                    SALES. ASSIST WITH SET UP OF PETROLEUM INSTITUTE OF THAILAND IN CO-OPE­ RATION
                                    WITH PCIAC. INTRODUCTION OF CANADIAN TECHNOLOGY AND TRAINING SERVICES THROUGH
                                    THE INSTITUTE. TRACKING: ACTIVITIES UNDERTAKEN IN QUARTER: QUARTER: 1 ARRANGE
                                    DINNER FOR VISIT OF TECHNICAL EXPERTS FROM PCIAC. QUARTER: 2 QUARTER: 3 QUARTER:
                                    4 QUARTERLY RESULTS REPORTED: 20 SENIOR OFFICIALS IN OIL AND GAS INDUSTRY ATTENDED.
                                    CDN OIL/GAS TECHNOLOGY WAS WELL PROMOTED IN THIS EVENT. 1

                                </t>
                            </page>
                        </txtmap>
                    </mets:xmlData>
                </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:dmdSec>
            <mets:amdSec>
                <mets:techMD ID="jhove_distribution.b2148559_001">
                    <mets:mdRef LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="metadata/fulldocument.pdf.jhove.xml" MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="jhove"
                    />
                </mets:techMD>
                <mets:techMD ID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.1">
                    <mets:mdRef LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="metadata/b2148559_001_0001.jpg.jhove.xml" MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER"
                    OTHERMDTYPE="jhove" />
                </mets:techMD>
                <mets:techMD ID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.2">
                    <mets:mdRef LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="metadata/b2148559_001_0002.jpg.jhove.xml" MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER"
                    OTHERMDTYPE="jhove" />
                </mets:techMD>
                <mets:techMD ID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.3">
                    <mets:mdRef LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="metadata/b2148559_001_0003.jpg.jhove.xml" MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER"
                    OTHERMDTYPE="jhove" />
                </mets:techMD>
                <mets:techMD ID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.4">
                    <mets:mdRef LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="metadata/b2148559_001_0004.jpg.jhove.xml" MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER"
                    OTHERMDTYPE="jhove" />
                </mets:techMD>
                <mets:techMD ID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.5">
                    <mets:mdRef LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="metadata/b2148559_001_0005.jpg.jhove.xml" MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER"
                    OTHERMDTYPE="jhove" />
                </mets:techMD>
                <mets:techMD ID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.6">
                    <mets:mdRef LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="metadata/b2148559_001_0006.jpg.jhove.xml" MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER"
                    OTHERMDTYPE="jhove" />
                </mets:techMD>
                <mets:techMD ID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.7">
                    <mets:mdRef LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="metadata/b2148559_001_0007.jpg.jhove.xml" MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER"
                    OTHERMDTYPE="jhove" />
                </mets:techMD>
                <mets:techMD ID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.8">
                    <mets:mdRef LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="metadata/b2148559_001_0008.jpg.jhove.xml" MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER"
                    OTHERMDTYPE="jhove" />
                </mets:techMD>
                <mets:techMD ID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.9">
                    <mets:mdRef LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="metadata/b2148559_001_0009.jpg.jhove.xml" MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER"
                    OTHERMDTYPE="jhove" />
                </mets:techMD>
                <mets:techMD ID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.10">
                    <mets:mdRef LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="metadata/b2148559_001_0010.jpg.jhove.xml" MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER"
                    OTHERMDTYPE="jhove" />
                </mets:techMD>
            </mets:amdSec>
            <mets:fileSec>
                <mets:fileGrp USE="master">
                    <mets:file ADMID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.1" ID="master.b2148559_001.1" MIMETYPE="image/jpeg">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URN" xlink:href="b2148559_001_0001.jpg" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ADMID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.2" ID="master.b2148559_001.2" MIMETYPE="image/jpeg">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URN" xlink:href="b2148559_001_0002.jpg" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ADMID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.3" ID="master.b2148559_001.3" MIMETYPE="image/jpeg">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URN" xlink:href="b2148559_001_0003.jpg" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ADMID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.4" ID="master.b2148559_001.4" MIMETYPE="image/jpeg">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URN" xlink:href="b2148559_001_0004.jpg" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ADMID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.5" ID="master.b2148559_001.5" MIMETYPE="image/jpeg">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URN" xlink:href="b2148559_001_0005.jpg" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ADMID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.6" ID="master.b2148559_001.6" MIMETYPE="image/jpeg">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URN" xlink:href="b2148559_001_0006.jpg" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ADMID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.7" ID="master.b2148559_001.7" MIMETYPE="image/jpeg">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URN" xlink:href="b2148559_001_0007.jpg" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ADMID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.8" ID="master.b2148559_001.8" MIMETYPE="image/jpeg">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URN" xlink:href="b2148559_001_0008.jpg" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ADMID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.9" ID="master.b2148559_001.9" MIMETYPE="image/jpeg">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URN" xlink:href="b2148559_001_0009.jpg" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ADMID="jhove_master.b2148559_001.10" ID="master.b2148559_001.10" MIMETYPE="image/jpeg">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URN" xlink:href="b2148559_001_0010.jpg" />
                    </mets:file>
                </mets:fileGrp>
                <mets:fileGrp USE="distribution">
                    <mets:file ADMID="jhove_distribution.b2148559_001" ID="distribution.b2148559_001" MIMETYPE="application/pdf">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URN" xlink:href="fulldocument.pdf" />
                    </mets:file>
                </mets:fileGrp>
                <mets:fileGrp USE="canonical">
                    <mets:file ID="canonical.b2148559_001" MIMETYPE="text/html">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="http://gac.canadiana.ca/b2148559_001" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ID="canonical.b2148559_001.1" MIMETYPE="text/html">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="http://gac.canadiana.ca/b2148559_001.1" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ID="canonical.b2148559_001.2" MIMETYPE="text/html">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="http://gac.canadiana.ca/b2148559_001.2" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ID="canonical.b2148559_001.3" MIMETYPE="text/html">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="http://gac.canadiana.ca/b2148559_001.3" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ID="canonical.b2148559_001.4" MIMETYPE="text/html">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="http://gac.canadiana.ca/b2148559_001.4" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ID="canonical.b2148559_001.5" MIMETYPE="text/html">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="http://gac.canadiana.ca/b2148559_001.5" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ID="canonical.b2148559_001.6" MIMETYPE="text/html">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="http://gac.canadiana.ca/b2148559_001.6" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ID="canonical.b2148559_001.7" MIMETYPE="text/html">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="http://gac.canadiana.ca/b2148559_001.7" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ID="canonical.b2148559_001.8" MIMETYPE="text/html">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="http://gac.canadiana.ca/b2148559_001.8" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ID="canonical.b2148559_001.9" MIMETYPE="text/html">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="http://gac.canadiana.ca/b2148559_001.9" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ID="canonical.b2148559_001.10" MIMETYPE="text/html">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="http://gac.canadiana.ca/b2148559_001.10" />
                    </mets:file>
                </mets:fileGrp>
            </mets:fileSec>
            <mets:structMap TYPE="physical">
                <mets:div TYPE="issue" LABEL="avril-juin 1987" DMDID="dmd.b2148559_001">
                    <mets:fptr FILEID="distribution.b2148559_001" />
                    <mets:fptr FILEID="canonical.b2148559_001" />
                    <mets:div TYPE="page" LABEL="Image 1" DMDID="dmd.b2148559_001.1">
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="master.b2148559_001.1" />
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="canonical.b2148559_001.1" />
                    </mets:div>
                    <mets:div TYPE="page" LABEL="Image 2" DMDID="dmd.b2148559_001.2">
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="master.b2148559_001.2" />
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="canonical.b2148559_001.2" />
                    </mets:div>
                    <mets:div TYPE="page" LABEL="Image 3" DMDID="dmd.b2148559_001.3">
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="master.b2148559_001.3" />
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="canonical.b2148559_001.3" />
                    </mets:div>
                    <mets:div TYPE="page" LABEL="Image 4" DMDID="dmd.b2148559_001.4">
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="master.b2148559_001.4" />
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="canonical.b2148559_001.4" />
                    </mets:div>
                    <mets:div TYPE="page" LABEL="Image 5" DMDID="dmd.b2148559_001.5">
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="master.b2148559_001.5" />
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="canonical.b2148559_001.5" />
                    </mets:div>
                    <mets:div TYPE="page" LABEL="Image 6" DMDID="dmd.b2148559_001.6">
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="master.b2148559_001.6" />
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="canonical.b2148559_001.6" />
                    </mets:div>
                    <mets:div TYPE="page" LABEL="Image 7" DMDID="dmd.b2148559_001.7">
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="master.b2148559_001.7" />
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="canonical.b2148559_001.7" />
                    </mets:div>
                    <mets:div TYPE="page" LABEL="Image 8" DMDID="dmd.b2148559_001.8">
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="master.b2148559_001.8" />
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="canonical.b2148559_001.8" />
                    </mets:div>
                    <mets:div TYPE="page" LABEL="Image 9" DMDID="dmd.b2148559_001.9">
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="master.b2148559_001.9" />
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="canonical.b2148559_001.9" />
                    </mets:div>
                    <mets:div TYPE="page" LABEL="Image 10" DMDID="dmd.b2148559_001.10">
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="master.b2148559_001.10" />
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="canonical.b2148559_001.10" />
                    </mets:div>
                </mets:div>
            </mets:structMap>
        </mets:mets>
    </Appendix>
    <Appendix NUMBER="2">
        <mets:mets xmlns:mets="http://www.loc.gov/METS/" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:txt="http://canadiana.ca/schema/2012/xsd/txtmap"
        OBJID="00989">
            <mets:dmdSec ID="dmd.oocihm.00989">
                <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="DC">
                    <mets:xmlData>
                        <simpledc xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
                            <dc:title>Inquest on Mary Boyd, held at Provincial Lunatic Asylum, Toronto 5th and 6th of May,
                                1868 : evidence and correspondence in full : with comments of the Toronto Press.
                            </dc:title>
                            <dc:creator>Campbell, Duncan, 1811-1879.
                            </dc:creator>
                            <dc:date>1868</dc:date>
                            <dc:publisher>Toronto : [s.n.], 1868
                            </dc:publisher>
                            <dc:source>Scanned from a CIHM microfiche of the original publication held by the Public Archives
                                of Canada Library.
                            </dc:source>
                            <dc:identifier>00989</dc:identifier>
                            <dc:identifier>http://eco.canadiana.ca/view/oocihm.00989</dc:identifier>
                            <dc:language>eng</dc:language>
                            <dc:subject>Boyd, Mary</dc:subject>
                        </simpledc>
                    </mets:xmlData>
                </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:dmdSec>
            <mets:dmdSec ID="dmd.oocihm.00989.0001">
                <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="txtmap">
                    <mets:xmlData>
                        <txt:txtmap>
                            <txt:page>
                                <txt:t>
                                    Technical Notes / Notes techniques The institute has attempted to obtain the best original copy available for filming.
                                    Physical feetures of this copy which may alter any of the images in the reproduction
                                    are checked below Coloured covers/ Couvertures de couleur Coloured maps/ Cartes
                                    géographiques en couleur r--- Pages discoloured, stained or foxed/ L- Pages
                                    décoîorées, tachetées ou piquées r-, Tight bindîng (may cause shadows or L
                                    J distortion along interior margin)/ Reliure serré (peut causer de l'ombre
                                    ou de la distortion le long de da marge intérieure) Additional comments/ Orgi
                                    L. Commentaires supplémentaires L'institut a microfilmé le meilleur exemplaire
                                    qu'il lui a été possible de se procurer Certains défauts susceptibles de nuire
                                    à la qualité de la reproduction sont notés ci-dessous. Coloured pages/ LJ Pages
                                    de couleur Coloured plates/ Planches en couleur ri Show through/ Transparence
                                    Pages damaged/ Pages endommagées nal copy restored and laminated. Bibliograpnic
                                    Notes / Notes bibliographiques Only edition available/ Seule édition disponible
                                    Bound with other material/ Relié avec d'autres documents Cover title missing/
                                    'Le titre de couverture mancue Plates missing/ W . Des planches manquent Additional
                                    comments/ Commentaires supplémentaires ---- Pagination incorrect/ vo Erreurs
                                    de pagination Pages missing/ W Des pages manquent '- aps missing/ Des cartes
                                    géograohiques manouent Page iv msnumbered ii. Blank leaves which were added
                                    during restoration may apoear within the text. Whenevr possible, these have
                                    been omitted from filming.
                                </txt:t>
                            </txt:page>
                        </txt:txtmap>
                    </mets:xmlData>
                </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:dmdSec>
            <mets:fileSec>
                <mets:fileGrp USE="master">
                    <mets:file ID="master.oocihm.00989.0001" MIMETYPE="image/tiff">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URN" xlink:href="oocihm.00989.0001.tif" />
                    </mets:file>
                </mets:fileGrp>
                <mets:fileGrp USE="distribution">
                    <mets:file ID="distribution.oocihm.00989" MIMETYPE="application/pdf">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URN" xlink:href="oocihm.00989.pdf" />
                    </mets:file>
                </mets:fileGrp>
                <mets:fileGrp USE="canonical">
                    <mets:file ID="canonical.oocihm.00989" MIMETYPE="text/html">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="http://eco.canadiana.ca/view/oocihm.00989" />
                    </mets:file>
                    <mets:file ID="canonical.oocihm.00989.0001" MIMETYPE="text/html">
                        <mets:FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="http://eco.canadiana.ca/view/oocihm.00989.1" />
                    </mets:file>
                </mets:fileGrp>
            </mets:fileSec>
            <mets:structMap TYPE="physical">
                <mets:div ID="oocihm.00989" TYPE="document" LABEL="Inquest on Mary Boyd, held at Provincial Lunatic Asylum, Toronto 5th and 6th of May, 1868 : evidence and correspondence in full : with comments of the Toronto Press."
                DMDID="dmd.oocihm.00989">
                    <mets:fptr FILEID="distribution.oocihm.00989" />
                    <mets:fptr FILEID="canonical.oocihm.00989" />
                    <mets:div ID="oocihm.00989.0001" TYPE="page" LABEL="technical data sheet" DMDID="dmd.oocihm.00989.0001">
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="master.oocihm.00989.0001" />
                        <mets:fptr FILEID="canonical.oocihm.00989.0001" />
                    </mets:div>
                </mets:div>
            </mets:structMap>
        </mets:mets>
    </Appendix>
</METS_Profile>